{
    "id": "00a00eaaf0034cc98e9679aef1d01f15",
    "title": "At, in and to: exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "f50c2539ebe34d4fbb0fd1f444c56bd6",
            "title": "At, In And On",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "He gets …………………. the market by bike.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "to",
                        "at"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "My parents live ………………….Singapore.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "in",
                        "at"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I go ……………………. Singapore to see them whenever I can.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "to",
                        "in"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I went to see my parents ……………………. Singapore.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "to",
                        "in"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Let’s go …………………….. Marcel’s for coffee.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "to",
                        "at"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Let’s go and have tea ……………………. Smith’s.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "to",
                        "at"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Why are you looking ……………………. me like this?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "at",
                        "on"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Stop throwing stones …………………… the cats.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "at",
                        "to"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "When did you arrive …………………….. Mexico?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "to",
                        "in"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Could you shout …………………. James and tell him it is time he started.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "to",
                        "at"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}